<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no" ?>
<map>
	<region>
		<reg_num>01</reg_num>
		<description>North Atlantic. This watershed flows out into the Atlantic Ocean through many different rivers, such as the Connecticut, Hudson, and Potomac.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>02</reg_num>
		<description>North Atlantic. This watershed flows out into the Atlantic Ocean through many different rivers, such as the Connecticut, Hudson, and Potomac.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>03</reg_num>
		<description>Gulf Coast. This watershed includes the Brazos, San Antonio, and other rivers that drain into the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>04</reg_num>
		<description>Greak Lakes and St. Lawrence River. This watershed includes the 5 Great Lakes, which drain into the Atlantic Ocean through the St. Lawrence River.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>05</reg_num>
		<description>Mississippi-Missouri Drainage Basin. This watershed runs through all or parts of 31 states and empties into the Gulf of Mexico.  It’s the third largest watershed in the world. Formed by a group of six regional watersheds: the Upper Mississippi, Ohio, Tennessee, Lower Mississippi, Arkansas-Red-White, and Missouri.  The water from all these places eventually drains into the Gulf, so they act as one big watershed.</description>
	</region>

	<region>
		<reg_num>06</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	
	<region>
		<reg_num>07</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>08</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>09</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>10</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>11</reg_num>
		<description></description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>12</reg_num>
		<description>Gulf Coast. This watershed includes the Brazos, San Antonio, and other rivers that drain into the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>13</reg_num>
		<description>Rio Grande. This watershed includes the Rio Grande and Pecos Rivers, which flow east into the Gulf of Mexico.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>14</reg_num>
		<description>Colorado River. This watershed’s main body of water is the Colorado River, which crosses south into Mexico and empties into the Gulf of California.  </description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>15</reg_num>
		<description>Colorado River. This watershed’s main body of water is the Colorado River, which crosses south into Mexico and empties into the Gulf of California.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>16</reg_num>
		<description>Great Basin. This watershed is home to the largest desert in the U.S., and dry conditions cause much of the rain and snowfall to quickly evaporate.  Unlike other watersheds, this region’s water is trapped within its boundaries and will never reach the ocean. The largest bodies of water within the region are the Great Salt Lake and Lake Tahoe.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>17</reg_num>
		<description>Columbia River and Northwestern United States. This watershed carries water flowing from the Columbia and Snake Rivers into the Pacific Ocean.</description>
	</region>
	<region>
		<reg_num>18</reg_num>
		<description>California. This watershed drains into the Pacific Ocean through such rivers as the Sacramento and the San Joaquin.</description>
	</region>
</map>